So friends, if you want to invest your money in the market,
then join
Angel Broking right now because it
offers you a reliable
service and opening an account is also
absolutely free of cost. So join Angel
Broking today. The account opening link
is in the description. Open your account today. So, at
this moment, cement
companies can see this. Tomorrow there are going to be a lot of
results. The
journey of results will start with Reliance's numbers,
but after that we will do the banks. And then
Infosys will give its results on Sunday.
Vikram is going to be active. This Ashish Mage has
joined.
Kotak and ICICI Bank's
pornographic newsroom got stuck in me. I thought
I was all
made up. It takes so much hard work
and it is very good to use it on small companies.
[Music]
[Music] Let me
tell you,
in the year 1995, we will see a jump of about 30 percent. When you
come on the screen,
this is what
I will do at this time, it will be the
lowest in the last four quarters.
In the previous quarter, there was growth of about 1 percent to
24-25 percent.
You will see a little bit of alarm, which
is largely expected to remain because if the
slippages reduce from the last ₹4200 crore to
₹4000, then the figure will
improve or the acid quality Darshan Voice
President will improve because the recoveries will be
considerable and will be seen in the upgrade and quality
book and there is a speed
for which you are watching, the police is
also seeing in the stock, largely submitting, the
management's commentary will be on acid quality,
that commentary will also be good,
this is all positive for ICICI Bank,
friends, if you want to invest your money in the market, then
join
Angel Broking now because
you get a good, reliable
service and opening this account is also
absolutely free of cost, so join Angel
Broking today, the account opening link is
in the description, open your account today,
tell us the general map, Axis and Pass, AC, I
and Ko Topless numbers, we will talk about it
later because Unnati will come on Monday
and you had already given Vishu on the actress.
Tell me
what is the situation for ICICI and Kotkapura and is there a
mood to take the train on
Thursday
here
bring to front this
subscribe I think if someone
wants to play the result he could have
subscribed
10 subscribe
channel
press the subscribe button this is definitely number one den
networks in the context of treatment
WhatsApp Facebook Google assistant